[
    {
        "id":0,
        "name": "Ariados",
        "attack": 45,
        "defense": 35,
        "speed":75,
        "hp": 110,
        "current_hp": 110,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [16, 17, 20, 21],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Ariados_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Ariados_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Bug",
        "Moves": []
    },
    {
        "id":1,
        "name": "Crator",
        "attack": 45,
        "defense": 60,
        "speed":40,
        "hp": 160,
        "current_hp": 160,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [34, 12, 13, 1],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Crator_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Crator_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Dragon",
        "Moves": []
    },
    {
        "id":2,
        "name": "Criminalis",
        "attack": 25,
        "defense": 55,
        "speed": 90,
        "hp":140,
        "current_hp": 140,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [14, 15, 21, 30],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Criminalis_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Criminalis_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Flying",
        "Moves": []
    },
    {
        "id":3,
        "name": "Cryogonal",
        "attack": 60,
        "defense": 35,
        "speed":65,
        "hp": 110,
        "current_hp": 110,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [22, 23, 33, 21],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Cryogonal_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Cryogonal_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Ice",
        "Moves": []
    },
    {
        "id":4,
        "name": "Efflutal",
        "attack": 50,
        "defense": 50,
        "speed":60,
        "hp":  140,
        "current_hp": 140,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [24, 15, 20, 34],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Efflutal_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Efflutal_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Psychic",
        "Moves": []
    },
    {
        "id":5,
        "name": "Forbiddron",
        "attack": 30,
        "defense": 55,
        "speed": 60,
        "hp": 170,
        "current_hp": 170,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [28, 29, 8, 9],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Forbiddron_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Forbiddron_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Poison",
        "Moves": []
    },
    {
        "id":6,
        "name": "Hogriks",
        "attack": 25,
        "defense": 85,
        "speed":25,
        "hp": 180,
        "current_hp": 180,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [10, 11, 32, 18],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Hogriks_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Hogriks_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Rock",
        "Moves": []
    },
    {
        "id":7,
        "name": "Marelstorm",
        "attack": 40,
        "defense": 55,
        "speed":65,
        "hp": 130,
        "current_hp": 130,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [4, 5, 39, 21],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Marelstorm_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Marelstorm_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Water",
        "Moves": []
    },
    {
        "id":8,
        "name": "Pythonova",
        "attack": 45,
        "defense": 45,
        "speed":50,
        "hp": 140,
        "current_hp": 140,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [0, 1, 20, 34],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Pythonova_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Pythonova_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Fire",
        "Moves": []
    },
    {
        "id":9,
        "name": "Shorelorn",
        "attack": 40,
        "defense": 55,
        "speed":65,
        "hp": 140,
        "current_hp": 140,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [4, 5, 9, 32],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Shorelorn_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Shorelorn_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Water",
        "Moves": []
    },
    {
        "id":10,
        "name": "Tekagon",
        "attack": 40,
        "defense": 60,
        "speed": 30,
        "hp": 130,
        "current_hp": 130,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [10, 11, 12, 13],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Tekagon_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Tekagon_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Ground",
        "Moves": []
    },
    {
        "id":11,
        "name": "Titaneon",
        "attack": 20,
        "defense": 80,
        "speed": 30,
        "hp": 170,
        "current_hp": 170,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [39, 40, 34, 30],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Titaneon_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Titaneon_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Steel",
        "Moves": []
    },
    {
        "id":12,
        "name": "Tuffettry",
        "attack": 30,
        "defense": 55,
        "speed":70,
        "hp": 140,
        "current_hp": 140,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [37, 38, 31, 21],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Tuffettry_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Tuffettry_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Fairy",
        "Moves": []
    },
    {
        "id":13,
        "name": "Varanitor",
        "attack": 40,
        "defense": 50,
        "speed": 70,
        "hp": 140,
        "current_hp": 140,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [6, 7, 20, 19],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Varanitor_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Varanitor_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Grass",
        "Moves": []
    },
    {
        "id":14,
        "name": "Zapparition",
        "attack": 30,
        "defense": 65,
        "speed": 65,
        "hp": 150,
        "current_hp": 150,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [2, 3, 9, 31],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Zapparition_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Zapparition_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Electric",
        "Moves": []
    },
    {
        "id":15,
        "name": "Nemesusa",
        "attack": 47,
        "defense": 60,
        "speed": 45,
        "hp": 140,
        "current_hp": 140,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [20, 13, 35, 36],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Nemesusa_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Nemesusa_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Dark",
        "Moves": []
    },
    {
        "id":16,
        "name": "Solacor",
        "attack": 30,
        "defense": 80,
        "speed": 60,
        "hp": 130,
        "current_hp": 130,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [8, 9, 21, 40],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Solacor_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Solacor_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Ghost",
        "Moves": []
    },
    {
        "id":17,
        "name": "Avipex",
        "attack": 50,
        "defense": 40,
        "speed":70,
        "hp": 140,
        "current_hp": 140,
        "learnable_move_IDs": [26, 27, 15, 32],
        "sprite_front": "sprites/Avipex_Front.webp",
        "sprite_back": "sprites/Avipex_Back.webp",
        "Types": "Fighting",
        "Moves": []
    }
]